greeninbox.com 2018-09-06

# 

### Privacy policy

This is the privacy policy (" **Privacy Policy** ") that governs how we, Green Inbox. (" **Green Inbox** ", " **we** ", " **our** " or " **us** "), use Personal Information (defined below) that we collect, receive and store about individuals Users who visit, access and/or use (i) the website www.greeninbox.com (together with its subdomains, Content and Services, " **Site** "); and/or (ii) one of our mobile applications (" **App(s)** "). For the purposes hereof, all references to Site shall include App(s). This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms of Use, available at www.greeninbox.com/terms (" **Terms** "). Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meaning ascribed to them in the Terms. 

  1. **Introduction.** We have implemented this Privacy Policy because your privacy, and the privacy of other Users, is important to us. We provide this Privacy Policy explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your Personal Information is collected and used in connection with the Site and the Services that we offer through the Site. “ **Personal Information** ” means any information that may be used, either alone or in combination with other information, to personally identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a personal profile, an email address, telephone number, a home or other physical address, or other contact information. 
  2. **Consent and Modification.** By using the Site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to Green Inbox's processing of Personal Information for the purposes set forth herein. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time, which change will be effective ten (10) days following posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Your continued use of the Site ten (10) days following such posting means that you accept those changes. 
  3. **What Personal Information We Collect and How We Collect It.** We do not currently require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access to general information available on the Site. We do, however, receive and/or collect information from you in the following ways: 
    1. Account. In order to provide you with Services, you are required to first create an Account. We offer two ways to create an Account: 
      * Online Registration Form: You can complete and submit an online registration form which we make available on the Site. You will be asked to provide us with information such as your name, Site username, an email address or other selected Communication Channel. You may also and a password that you will use for your Account. You may also choose to provide additional information such as a logo, picture and other information in connection with your Account. We will use this information to distinguish you from other Users and to provide you with our Services. 
      * Third Party Account: You can click on a sign-in box that we display on the Site for Facebook, Twitter, or other designated third party websites (each a " **Third Party Account** "). Doing so will enable you to link your Account and your Third Party Account. If you choose this option, then a Third Party Account pop-up box will appear which you will need to approve in order to proceed. By linking your Account and your Third Party Account, you grant us authorization to collect the information that you make available to us from your Third Party Account. Please note that in order to use this option, you will need to have, and may need to be signed-in to, an existing Third Party Account. 
    2. Public Profile. The Site enables you to build a public profile in connection with your Account (" **Public Profile** "). Your Public Profile will include your name or your user name. You may also choose to include other information, such as a profile picture (which you may upload to the Site or import from your Third Party Account profile). 
    3. Feedback and 'Contact Us' Information. If you send us Feedback or a "Contact Us" request, you may be required to provide us with information such as your name, Site username and email address. We will receive and store such information as well as any other Personal Information you disclose, which we will use to reply to you. 
    4. Services. We collect, receive and store Personal Information in connection with the Services that we provide. Such information may include, without limitation: a mobile phone number, the email addresses of your Friends, hobbies and other information. Your participation in any Services is optional and you at all times have the choice of choosing whether to provide any related Personal Information. 
    5. User Submissions. If you post or publish User Submissions, then we will receive and store such Content, whether or not it includes Personal Information. We collect this information so that we can provide you with the Services. 
    6. Invite-a-Friend Service. If you choose to participate in our Invite-a-Friend Service, whereby we enable you to refer Friends to the Site, then you will need to provide us with the email addresses of the Friends that you wish to refer. 
    7. Log Files. The Site may make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, clicked pages and any other information your browser may send to us. We may use such information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user's movement around the Site, and gather demographic information. 
    8. Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies. Some of our Site pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A " **cookie** " is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a User. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. 
    9. Visiting the Site. In general, you may visit certain parts of this Site without identifying or revealing any information about yourself. 
  4. **Publicly Available Information.**
    1. User Submissions. The Site permits the submission, hosting, posting, publishing, transmit and sharing of User Submissions to members of the Circle. You acknowledge and agree that certain User Submissions will become publicly published Content and will be available to all members of the Circle. This is the case even if your User Submission contains Personal Information. Please note that if you publish your contact information as a part of your User Submission or Public Profile, you may receive unsolicited messages from Users, members of the Circle or other third parties. We therefore encourage you to post and publish only information you are sure you want to be accessible to anyone. 
    2. Public Profile. Your Public Profile will be publicly available to other Users, the Circle. Link between User Submissions and Public Profile. Please note that some or all of your Public Profile may be displayed next to or in connection with your User Submissions. 
  5. **The Way We Use Personal Information.** If you submit or we collect Personal Information through the Site, then such Personal Information may be used in the following ways: 
    1. We will use your Personal Information to provide and improve our Site and Services to you, to contact you in connection with the Site and Services that you have registered for, and to identify and authenticate your access to the parts of the Site and specific Services that you are authorized to access. 
    2. We may use your designated email address(es) to send you (i) updates or news regarding the Site and Services, and (ii) respond to a "Contact Us" or queries. You may easily remove yourself from our mailing list, and each email you will receive from us will contain clear instructions on how to do so. You may also choose not to receive emails of this type. 
    3. If you choose to participate in the Invite-a-Friend Service, we will use the contact information that you provide us to automatically send your Friend(s) inviting them to visit the Site. We will include your name in the invitation email. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending the invitation email and tracking the success of whether your Friend registers an Account. 
    4. If you include Personal Information in an inquiry, response, message, or comment, including but not limited to User Submission, that you send or post to another User or member of the Circle, then such Personal Information will be disclosed to such persons. 
    5. We may transfer your Personal Information within Green Inbox or to Green Inbox's third-party service providers (such as hosting providers), but only to provide the Services to you. This information may be transferred to other countries around the world. We use commercially reasonable efforts to only engage or interact with third party service providers that post a Privacy Policy governing their processing of Personal Information. 
    6. We may transfer your Personal Information to our subsidiaries or affiliated companies for the purpose of storing or processing such information on our behalf. Such information may be transferred to other countries around the world. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy, and use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
    7. We may disclose your Personal Information or any information you submitted via the Site if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; (ii) enforce our Terms including investigations of potential violations thereof; (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud or security issues; or (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Green Inbox, its Users, yourself or the public. 
    8. In most cases, we retain your Personal Information so that you, for instance, can return to view prior User Submissions you have sent or received. In addition, if a User asks us to deactivate his Account, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to remove the data from our servers. Despite such removal, portions of the data may remain on our production and back-up servers. 
  6. **Use of Anonymous Information.** We may use Anonymous Information (defined below) or disclose it to third party service providers in order to improve our Services and enhance your experience with the Site. We may also disclose Anonymous Information (with or without compensation) to third parties, including advertisers and partners, for purposes including, but not limited to, targeting advertisements. " **Anonymous Information** " means information which does not enable identification of an individual User, such as aggregated information about use of the Site. 
  7. **Opting-Out.** You may choose not to receive future promotional, updates, or other communication from us. 
  8. **Choice.** At all times, you may choose whether or not to provide or disclose Personal Information. The notices that we provide on the Site in circumstances where we collect Personal Information should help you make this choice. 
  9. **Access/Accuracy.** To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Green Inbox wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. You may use the Site tools to remove or modify certain information such as your password. 
  10. **Links to Other Sites.** If you are a registered User, the Site allows you to post and publish a link to Events or the Site on other sites (for example, Facebook or Twitter). The Site may also contain links to third party websites that are not owned or controlled by Green Inbox. Other websites may also reference or link to the Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites, and you visit them at your own risk. 
  11. **Children's Privacy.** The Site is not structured to attract individuals under the age of 13. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under 13 years, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any such information, please contact us. 
  12. **Security.** The security of Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards, including the use of appropriate administrative, physical and technical safeguards, to protect the Personal Information submitted to us. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security or confidentiality. If you have any questions about security on the Site, you can contact us. 
  13. **In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy.** In the event that Green Inbox is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Site as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, assignment for the benefit of creditors or comparable event, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used. In any of the circumstances described in this paragraph, the information will be subject to the privacy policy of the purchaser or assignee. 
  14. **Your California Privacy Rights.** California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Green Inbox who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year. 
  15. **Commitment.** We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and we are constantly evolving our Site to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy or your Personal Information, please contact us. 

**Last updated: Dec 15th, 2013**
